This time,
I want to do it right, Andrew.
Just think of it like
you didn't fall for him.
That's easy, right?
Yvette, I know in my heart
that she could never do this
to herself.
So, who would do this?
We will never know
until she wakes up.
Why doesn't his name show up
in our files?
His name is not real.
What's his name?
Kang Dae-Hyun.
Joey, listen carefully.
Jin Ho is a criminal.
Don't go with him. Joey!
I know I have a lot
of explaining to do.
I have to go.
I think he knows Berdugo.
How can we find that out?
I thought of another way.
[GRUNTS]
Are you really trying to test
my patience?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Clearly, you're upset again.
What did I do this time?
Now, you're asking?
Why didn't you tell me
that you're leaving?
I didn't know
that I'm a prisoner here.
You're not.
You're acting like you're not
part of this operation.
Am I?
All I do is watch what is
happening in the factory.
That's an important task!
But you know I can do more
than babysit!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Theresa.
If you give me a chance
to talk to Berdugo,
I can make you trust me
to do bigger responsibilities
with bigger rewards.
He'll be here tomorrow
to check our operations,
so you better make sure
to make a good impression.
My name is on the line here,
so don't ruin your chance.
I won't.
Oh, dear...
you haven't slept yet.
Why are you still awake?
Mom...
I really can't sleep,
so I'm just doing some thinking.
How about you?
Ma'am Yvette asked me to
accompany her to the hospital.
Mom, how's Ma'am Rebecca?
She's out of the ICU.
She's in a private room now.
Her condition is improving,
but she's still unconscious.
Is Andrew there?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, he's still watching over
his mother.
How is he? Is he okay?
You know, you're both asking
the same question.
He asked me how you were.
I told him...
you're fine.
But is that true, child?
Are you really okay?
Of course,
why wouldn't I be?
Because it's obvious
that you're concerned.
The truth is, dear,
it's clear that Boss Idol
is confused about what happened
to his mother.
He can't understand
how Ma'am Rebecca ended up
like this.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom, about Ma'am Yvette's
husband...
The suspicion you had about him,
did you tell her?
I don't know
if I should say something.
Child, Sir Tomas seems fine.
He's good to his family,
especially to Andrew.
It's hard to make accusations.
Maybe we're just giving
too much meaning
to what Ma'am Rebecca said.
I hope so, Mom.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I hope Ma'am Rebecca
recovers soon.
So, Andrew won't worry anymore.
- That's right.
- So...
that we'll finally
know the truth
about what really happened.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom, I always want
to be like you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
The person who can say
everything.
But...
I don't know why,
but when it comes to Joey,
I can't admit it.
Do you still love her?
Actually, I already love
someone else,
family,
friends like you.
You love me already?
Before, I wanted to ask you
about work...
but now it's personal.
Mom, please wake up.
I really need your advice.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom?
Mom, can you hear me?
Squeeze my hand if you do.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, good morning! Welcome back!
Your motorpart is good now.
Finally!
You took care of my baby, right?
Yes, Sir!
Sir, have seat.
Thank you.
[♪INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING♪]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello, Sir?
This is the shop.
Are you sure that's the Korean
we're looking for?
- Yes.
- Okay, thanks.
I'm on my way.
Dad...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
you're leaving?
You're going out?
It's dangerous,
someone might see you.
I'll be careful.
And I'm prepared.
Dad, even so.
I'll come with you.
Dad, please.
You're going
to see Jin Ho, right?
I'm coming with you.
No, you shouldn't.
It's dangerous
and I'm just going to tail him.
Oh, that's even better.
You're just going to follow him.
Please say yes, Dad.
I promise, I will behave.
I won't pester you.
I just want to see for myself
if what you said
about Jin Ho is true
that he's a criminal
and part of the syndicate.
What happened was reflexive
movement.
These are automatic responses
to stimuli
such as finger twitching
and response to touch
and loud noises.
I held mom's hand.
That explains it.
But don't worry.
That's a good sign
because at least,
we know the patient's body
still reacts,
even involuntarily.
We'll just monitor her.
Thank you, Doc.
I'll leave you for now.
All right, thank you.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom...
I still don't know
how this happened to you.
But I promise you...
I'll do everything.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Make sure everything
is in order, Lisa.
You're still making up
for your past mistakes.
I know, Berdugo.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I also want to meet the man
you brought into the group.
Yes, of course.
Matias said
he doesn't trust that man.
Matias doesn't trust anyone.
You know, he's paranoid.
But believe me...
You can trust my guy.
I'll be the judge of that.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
There he is.
Do you want me to go straight
to him, ask him?
"Where's Berdugo?"
No!
You said you'd behave, remember?
Stay here!
You're so tense, Dad.
I'm just joking, sorry.
You and your jokes!
You know this is serious.
I want my normal life back.
I don't want to keep hiding.
I also want Berdugo's
iniquity to end.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
You ready to go?
Who is he talking to?
Let's follow him.
Never say die?
Never say die.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, move closer.
They might get away.
This is near enough.
They might notice us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dad, why did they stop?
I don't know.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are we going?
Are we meeting Berdugo here?
No.
I'm just taking a breather.
Are you worried about me
meeting him?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't be.
You don't know him like I do.
Even after all these years
in this job,
I still get intimidated by him.
If you are this scared,
why don't you take
my suggestion?
We can be our own boss
back in Korea.
We both know the ins and outs
of this business.
I like what I do.
And besides,
you can't just get out
of Berdugo's organization.
Once you're in,
you can never leave.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
Joey, hide!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[♪SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING♪]
[CAT SNARLS]
Dad, that's Theresa!
She's the woman Jin Ho
wants to capture.
And she's the woman
I told you about
who was there when Ramon
was killed!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you sure that's the woman
in your video?
Yes, Dad, that's her!
[REVVING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's weird.
What?
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't mind them.
Let's just go back.
Berdugo might be there already.
No, I really think
we're being followed.
Are you sure?
That car was parked behind us.
I think something's wrong.
I have a bad feeling about this.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING]
Dad, why did you stop?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
They'll escape!
Looks like they realized
we were following them.
Forget it.
We'll just get into trouble.
But, Dad, this is our chance!
My child...
Your safety is more important
to me.
Let them go.
We might just get into trouble.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you sure you didn't
notice anything
the day something happened
to mommy?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe she ate something?
No, nothing.
We ate the same food.
Who were here that day?
Me, Ma'am Clarissa, the kids,
Ma'am Yvette, and Sir Tomas.
Okay, thank you.
He's unbelievable, Dad.
We treated him as a friend
but in return,
he did that to us?
Why would he do that, Dad?
Because he was looking
for Theresa.
Now, you became the key
when he saw your video.
If they really know each other,
then they're together
in the syndicate.
Does that mean...
Jin Ho might have told Theresa
that I was the one
who took the video?
But why wouldn't he reveal
my location?
Maybe...
Maybe he used our friendship
to get close to Theresa,
not to hurt me, Dad.
We don't know for sure.
We don't know
what their plan is.
But what's important is
to catch them
so nothing happens to you.
"Nothing happens"?
Miguel, you keep going out.
Someone might see you.
Are you two planning
something again?
You're just...
too suspicious.
Let's just go upstairs.
- Okay? Let's go upstairs.
- You're planning something...
No, you're just too suspicious.
Joey?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[KNOCK ON THE DOOR]
Kisses?
Uncle Andrew...
How are you?
I know you miss
your grandmother...
because I do too.
Will it take long
before she comes home?
I don't know.
But I'm sure
she'll get better,
because many people are waiting
for her, like you.
She misses grandmother too,
Uncle.
Of course.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Anyways, I have to go.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why aren't the shipments
for tomorrow packed yet?
Shouldn't they be ready?
Idiots!
Don't scold them.
I told them that I will check
the goods first.
Relax.
I'll do that later.
Go ahead, go back there now.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What if Berdugo asks?
You know this isn't how
our operation works, right?
Where did you come from?
Looks like you were just busy
flirting.
Don't talk to me like that.
So what?
I don't care what you do.
What matters to me
is this operation!
Don't do that again.
Are you going to fight me?
Stop speaking in English.
What are you talking about?
You've got nothing to brag
about.
Tell your dog to behave.
Or he's gonna get it from me.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What's this?
Oh, no!
Kisses...
What happened?
I broke it, Harris.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
We can fix it.
We'll just ask mommy to fix it,
okay?
Let me see.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait, what's this?
What's this?
I found this inside.
Looks like a camera.
[THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[THUDS AND CLACKS]
Stop this nonsense!
Is this how you really are
when I'm not here?
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Is this how you handle
this place?
It's not our fault.
I'm not talking to you.
Sorry about that, Berdugo.
They just hate each other.
I promise this is the first
and the last time
that this will happen.
I hope so.
Because if not,
I'll fix it myself.
And I promise you...
you won't like it.
I don't want to waste my time.
Let's start the meeting.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
We're not done yet.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- My child...
- Mom...
Are you okay?
You've been pacing around.
No, I'm just trying to reach
10,000 steps to stay sexy.
Oh, my daughter's
really grown up.
You're conscious
of your body now.
Who are you trying
to look good for?
- Andrew?
- Andrew? No!
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
He's just my friend.
Dear, you're being way
too defensive.
You know, I have no problems
with that.
Just don't forget
your priorities,
especially your studies.
Speaking of Andrew,
have you talked
to your boyfriend...
I mean, your friend yet?
Not yet. Why?
Andrew is going through
something heavy right now.
Aren't you concerned?
Call him.
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am Zoey!
Hi!
Where's Andrew?
He went to his room.
- Ah, okay.
- All right, Ma'am.
Okay, thanks.
[PHONE RINGING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey!
Hi!
Why are you calling Andrew?
Zoey?
Where's Andrew?
He's busy.
He's preparing things to bring
to the hospital
for Mommy Rebecca.
"Mommy Rebecca?"
Ah, yes.
That's what I used to call her
when Andrew and I were together.
I guess I should get used
to calling her that again,
especially now that Andrew
and I are doing okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Is someone looking for my
corpse?
Maybe Berdugo thinks
differently.
Then let's bury Miguel.
- What happened to you?
- I wanted to see you.
Enjoy your coffee
because it's your last.
You're doomed.
Don't leave yet.
I'm curious
if this thing really works.
You are Kang Dae-Hyun, correct?
I have a problem.
The cops already know
who I really am.
Good thing no one saw me.
I feel I'm being haunted.
I think I saw Delgado.
What?